So, what I am holding in my hand is a thirty-five millimeter negative carrier.
And, what you do with this is you put your negative in here and you close it.
Put this top part back on.
Now, there are a million designs of these type of carriers, but what I am showing you today is a design for this one.
This is pretty common actually.
The thing you want to remember, is to make sure that all the pieces fit.
This notch should meet with this notch.
What you do not want to do is have something that looks kind of wrong.
Like the notches are not fitting correctly.
When you are putting your negative in here, you really want to take your time.
I like doing it on a light table.
When I talk about printing, I am going to show how to do it on the light table.
But for today, I just want to show you how this enlarger works.
The notches me.
I pull the head open, and what I do is I slide it in and I make sure it fits perfectly.
Thus, the light can shine through my negative onto my photographic paper and I am on my way to making a print.